(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Van's right.
It's my fault.
I was being selfish.
I didn't think about
how you would feel.
I'm really sorry, guys.
Wait
was Dave with you?
He hasn't come back
from his classes.
Let's look for him!
Dave, where have you been?
I needed fresh air after class.
On the verge of Bloody Night?
Do I need to be a demon like them?
Do I need to be more
savage than them?
I am the Supreme Student Secretary.
I have the right to object
to your decisions.
Let us talk about the big event
that's going to happen in this school.
And we will call it.
Bloody Week.
Where killing is legal in
a span of a week.
At any time.
We know that you know HU's secrets.
I will do everything in my power so
all of you can leave this hellhole.
What happened to you?
I was one of their test subjects for
the serum that they're making.
This is an order from the SSG President
if I say something
you answer quickly.
Got it?
You know
you just might be my Achilles' heel.
Ms. Shion.
Just tell me where the
laboratory is hidden.
Come with me.
I'll show you.
Where's the laboratory?
Just tell me where
the laboratory is.
The laboratory you're
looking for is...
It's hidden at...
Just tell me where it is please.
What are you doing?
What the fuck!
She’s going to die anyway.
I saved her from her suffering.
Why are you doing this
you crazy bitch?
I'm just saving you.
Us.
Stay away from Alvarez.
Chill
hurting me won't do you any good.
I'm just saving you.
Us.
Stay away from Alvarez.
Listen, Zein.
If you accept Ace's offer
you'll be able to find out
where the hidden laboratory is.
Secret lab.
Being the SSG secretary
has its benefits.
You'll know everything.
Learn things no one else can.
Once you take this position
you'll have control
and people will fear you for it.
They're heartless!
Monsters!
You're just like them.
You're a monster too.
We thought you're
the next Samantha
but just like her,
you can't change anything.
Why was she able to do something?
I thought...
you're like Samantha.
But you're not.
You're a coward.
Who is this Samantha
they keep mentioning?
Why are they calling
me her name?
Who is she?
Her name is Samantha.
We all thought it would last forever.
But nothing is for sure here in Hell U
except for bloodshed and death.
What's worse is...
the demons became more brutal.
Are you going to help us or not?
Us? There are others?
Wait!
Where are you going?
I still have a lot of questions left.
Where is the lab?
Just tell me where it is please!
It's better to be careful, Zein.
Because our lives are in your hands.
Don't ever cross the line with them.
I've been explaining this multiple times
and you still can't understand?
My throat is hurting
from all these lectures!
How are you this stupid?
Get a grip!
What do you want to happen?
Are you going to be
this stupid forever?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
That's just a piece of cake, idiot!
You never listen to any of it
that's why it doesn't
seep into your brain!
Airhead!
Enough. I told you
to stop it, didn't I?
How dare you!
You stupid girl!
You brain doesn't absorb
anything doesn't it?
I said stop it!
I'm so tired of this!
You're always picking on me.
Embarrassing me.
I have no face to show
because of you.
If I'm stupid
and you're smart?
Prove it to me and answer this question.
When do you think
you're going to die?
I'm aware a lot will
happen this Bloody Week.
But I didn't expect it would be this bad.
The week has barely started
but this is already unbearable to me.
How worse can it get in the incoming days?
What are the horrors in store for us?
Zein!
I'm going to kill you!
There are moments
where I start to lose hope.
that we'll make it out
of Hell University alive.
My friends are my only source of strength
to continue fighting.
Hey...
you're spacing out again.
We're going to get through this.
Where are they?
You know what, Zein
with everything going on.
My fear and nervousness
lessens when we're together.
Just like yesterday
you made us worry
but we trust you.
Didn't we make a promise
that we'll stick together?
I need to go.
I thought we'll stick together?
We are sticking together
we'll see each other again.
But I need to do something.
You know as a sexytary.
I like that. Sexytary.
And Van's there.
You won't be alone.
So don't worry too much, okay?
Go on.
Do a good job, Ms. Sexytary.
Come join us, Zein!
Catch this, Zein!
- Bye, Zein.
- Bye.
- She's so busy.
- Hurry!
Here, Dave.
Nice one.
I'm still supposed to be angry at him
after he didn't do anything
to stop Bloody Week.
But I don't know.
I'm still impressed by his
bravery and composure
amidst the chaos.
He's built different.
I still can't believe he
protected me from Madam Violet.
At least he's still fair.
Does he think of me as a friend?
Alex Mendoza, Supremo.
X on it, Ms. Shion.
Do it!
But why?
He's still alive.
You're wasting our time here, Ms. Shion.
If you were in my shoes
what would you do?
I would save him.
Okay.
Let's say we help him
and he lives.
What do you think will happen next?
That'll be all?
Will his enemies let him stay alive?
But...
Why waste my time with someone
who’s supposed to be dead?
We can't save everyone, Ms. Shion.
You and Matt said the same thing.
I'm going to kill you!
Zein!
Killing is legal now.
You might get hurt from
stepping in their fight!
We can't save everybody Zein!
Matt said the same thing.
Sir Alvarez
you're ten minutes late
for your next subject.
I needed to do something, Supremo.
I'm rushing over there.
Excuse me.
What's your relationship with him?
Nothing.
Supremo.
I've secured the files.
Um... Supremo
is there anything else
you need me to do?
None.
You're good.
Angelica, show me through it.
Okay.
I can review.
You can leave.
But my duty is not done.
Excuse me?
Angelica and I can handle it.
We can take it from here.
Really? Angelica?
Supremo called her by her first name
while he calls me by my surname?
What am I even talking aboout?
Matthew might be looking for you.
Obviously.
They're so annoying!
Who does he think he is?
You have a lot of nerve, Supremo.
This one, solve this.
Try me.
Don't you dare!
Let me go!
Be quiet!
Shut up, stay away.
Get me out of this hell!
Let go off me!
If you don't
I'll kill this girl!
Supremo...
Let's leave, Supremo.
I'm not kidding!
How could I forget?
Other people's lives have no value to them.
Zein!
Even my life.
Why would he help me?
Let her go!
I'm just his secretary.
Let me go!
Who are you going to kill again?
Zein!
Who'll die now?
What's happening to you, Zein?
Almost...
he's still alive.
Zein.
You're bleeding.
This won't kill me.
Let me out of this hellhole!
The wound is shallow.
What happened to
you earlier, Zein?
I don't know.
It's like I was possessed.
Even your eyes were
different earlier.
It's like the eyes of a killer.
That's too much.
She didn't kill anyone,
Jerome. Stop it.
I know that
but...
she became different.
I even hesitated if
I should help Matt
but I was afraid that
you might stab me.
Zein won't do that.
But you were a different
person earlier, Zein.
I felt your rage.
It's like you turned
into a monster.
Me?
A monster?
You're wasting your
time, nurse Cha.
That's just a flesh wound.
Who was that?
That's Dr. Razon.
There's a doctor here?
He doesn't seem to care
about us students.
What happened?
Where have you been?
I got stuck outside.
I was hiding until
the chaos stopped.
Where are they?
Don't tell me...
This can't be.
I shouldn't think this way.
But if they're not in their rooms
that only means one thing.
This has been going
on for a while.
Van?
They leave every night.
What?
We need to find them!
Zein
not tonight, please.
Van
what is happening?
Have you known they were
sneaking out all this time?
I'm scared, Zein.
Of what?
I've been waking up at night
recurringly with the boys gone.
Sometimes Matt
then Dave
and Jerome.
I don't know where
they're sneaking off to.
But they keep leaving
during Bloody Night.
I'll figure out where they keep going to.
Zein, please.
Van...
We're the only ones here.
Let's stick together.
Just this night.
Please.
Please, Zein.
Didn't we already talk about this, Van?
This is only for emergencies.
We need to survive Bloody Week
if we want to leave this place.
Our lives are in danger, Zein.
If we don't help ourselves
who will help us?
Help!
Help me!
Jerome?
Please!
Jerome!
Help me!
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
♪ Happy birthday. ♪
Oh my god, Jerome.
You guys scared me there!
Happy birthday, Ms. Secretary!
Happy birthday!
Thank you so much guys!
I forgot my own birhtday.
It's because you have too
much on your mind!
Good thing we thought about you.
Did we do a good job?
Super!
Thank you so much guys.
But you didn't have to.
Of course, Zein.
Go on, Matt. Aren't you
going to greet Zein?
He's right, your saliva
will dry up.
I'm doing it, guys.
That's our boy.
Happy birthday, Zein.
That's our boy!
Thank you, Matt.
She's turning red!
I think she's more than okay.
Let's go, Zein. Blow the candle?
Here she comes.
Make a wish.
Yey!
Happy birthday!
Let's eat!
Let's go!
And because it's your
birthday, sit in the middle.
Our princess.
Thank you, guys.
Who cooked this?
Of course, there's no one but Mia!
Wow, Mia!
Okay?
Yeah.
It says in the student records
that the percentage of absentees are high.
List it down. Okay?
Prepare it.
I'll take care of it.
Check it properly since you volunteered.
Make sure you won't make any mistakes
or Supremo will reprimand you again.
Fine.
Since you guys can’t expect anything
from your good for nothing secretary.
Hey
why are you so damn happy?
That's none of your business.
Watch your words.
Onel!
What's the occassion?
I think it's better if you
ask Ms. Secretary, Supremo.
What? I don't know anything.
Okay, can somebody just tell me
what we're supposed
to be celebrating?
Nevermind.
Just leave!
All of you.
Why are you so happy?
Why are you smiling?
Am I not allowed to?
You know
instead of wasting your time
thinking about why I'm smiling
you should focus on Bloody Week.
Cause what's happening around us
should be taken seriously.
Fine.
Just leave me alone.
Gladly.
I said leave.
Okay, I'm leaving.
So impatient.
I'm leaving.
Bye!
Why does he care if I'm smiling?
He should mind his own business.
Just like yesterday
when someone tried to kill
me and he didn't do anything.
He was right.
You're weird.
Um... Zein right?
You amaze me.
You're really one of a kind.
I saw how you defended yourself yesterday.
I can only tell you one thing
he believes in you.
Even if he wanted to help you
he restrained himself from doing it.
I had my doubts but.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry
I've been blabbering.
Okay,
I'll go ahead.
What is she talking about?
Do I have the wrong impression about Ace?
Why are people acting so weird today?
It could've been perfect.
If only someone added sugar in the cake.
True.
It was already tastleless,
but it collapsed too!
What a waste.
I know, it's my fault.
I got tensed and distracted by the smoke
that's why I forgot to add in sugar.
I'm sorry, Zein. I'm sorry.
At least we decorated it well.
It looked like an actual birthday cake.
He's right.
Right, Matt?
And it's the thought that counts.
You liked it, didn't you, Zein?
Of course.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you, guys.
I couldn't ask for more.
You guys look like you're having fun.
Here he is again.
But I need my secretary.
Can't you function without your secretary?
So I'm still his secretary, huh?
I thought I was already replaced.
Sorry guys,
duty calls.
You can go ahead.
Let's see each other at the dorm later.
Okay?
Um, okay.
What do you need?
You really won't tell me about it?
Did I really have to look into it?
Do you enjoy giving me a hard time?
I knew there was
something about your smile.
You made my head hurt from thinking.
Huh?
Happy birthday...
Zein.
I always thought Ace ignored my existance.
That he didn't care.
But with three words,
he made me feel seen.
And for whatever reason, I appreciate it.
Good morning, students.
What is this again?
Do you find Bloody Week a little boring?
Then let's play a game.
To make Bloody Week more exciting!
Look inside your lockers.
On the paper are names you have to kill
before the time runs out.
If you didn't get a name.
You are chosen to die.
Did you know about this?
No.
Where are we going?
Check your locker.
Supremo's here. Let's go!
Open it.
Do I have to?
Do I have to do this?
Is this really happening?
You can check it.
I'll be here with you, okay?
I'll stay with you.
Hey...
Hey.
Calm down.
Calm down, breathe.
Calm down, okay?
What if I pick one of my friends?
Or your name?
Don't look too far, okay?
Let's check it first
then we'll see from there.
Okay?
For you.
What is it?
A gift.
For Bloody Night.
There's nothing written here.
Nothing.
It will last one whole week!
And we will call it Bloody Week.
Where killing is legal for one whole week.
I'm tired of you!
I'm always you're target!
I'm done with you embarassing me.
- Be quiet. Don't come near us.
- Help me!
Let me out of this hellhole!
If you get targeted by the gangs
you will never find peace again.
No!
I tried to ignore the
recurring disappearance
of my friends during Bloody Night.
But I can't turn a blind eye anymore.
I need to know what's
happening with my friends.
Hoy!
Did you hear that?
Something moved back there.
That's just the cat.
Is he upstairs?
Can we really trust him?
He's instantly the co-leader?
That doesn't make sense.
What else can we do?
Boss likes him.
And let's give him a chance.
Boss sees something in him.
I hope he's right...
This gang war has been tiring
we always have to be one
step ahead of the DGW.
Let's go.
Let’s go.
Let's hurry before Boss gets mad.
I want you to see everything.
Who is Van talking to?
That's Liam.
Who was written in your paper?
Anonymous.
There are things we should keep hidden.
You're drunk.
So what if I'm drunk?
Even if I'm drunk.
I know
that you're still beautiful.
You promised that when you find the
man you'll love for the rest of your life
you'll love him forever.
The wound is deep!
Doc!
Please hurry!
Open the door!
We're sorry but the clinic is closed today.
Ms. Shion!